Smart Planner Readme:In the Smart Planner app, you can plan your agenda with rich resources from Foursquare venue database. When planning an activity, you are able to search places in your neighborhood or in any specific location and add to your plan list. You’ll be able to view your activities in a table or a calendar. 

Below are a few tips on using the app:
1. The first view of the app is the table view of all your saved plans, tap the tab below to switch to the calendar view

2. In the calendar view, all plans in the current month will be displayed in a list. And a day in calendar will be highlighted in yellow if there’s a plan on that day.

3. In the calendar view, click “next month” and “last month” to navigate among different months

4. In both table view and calendar view, you can delete a plan by swiping on the table row and tap “Delete”. Click the “Add” Button on the top right to add a new plan

6. In the plan creation view, you should search a place first. If you need to search nearby, leave the switch on. Otherwise, tap the switch off and fill in “Search Area”

7. When you select a location, the app navigates to a detail page where you can confirm the venue information and select and date. After completed, click the button to save your plan!